Guide to the Athletics Department Records
University of Houston Libraries
Athletics Department Records
1950-2014
2009-006
University of Houston. Athletics Department
15.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
These records contain 9 boxes, 9 oversize folders and 1 scrapbook, all relating to the various athletic teams of the University of Houston. A significant portion of this material was given to the archives from the University Print Plant.
Historical Note:
The University of Houston’s first athletic teams existed merely as student extracurricular activities during its years as the Houston Junior College (1927 -1934), and consisted of a girl’s basketball team, an ice hockey team, and a football team.
Over the years, as enrollment and construction increased at the university, so did the desire for a great athletics program. The first year of intercollegiate sports was 1946.
Since that time the University of Houston Department of Athletics has grown tremendously, and has seen the construction of eight on-campus facilities for the purpose of supporting its student athletes.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston -- Sports; University of Houston -- Sports -- History; University of Houston. Athletics Department
Genre/Form of Material:
Ephemera; Newsletters; Newspapers; Pamphlets; Programs (documents)
Topical Term:
Football -- Texas -- Houston
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Related Materials:
University of Houston Sports Championship Publications digital collection http://digital.lib.uh.edu/collection/champ
Scope and Contents
These records contain 9 boxes, 9 oversize folders and 1 scrapbook, all relating to the various athletic teams of the University of Houston. A significant portion of this material was given to the archives from the University Print Plant. Material includes correspondence, stationery, publications, program guides, press guides, newspaper clippings, handbooks, and scrapbooks. This collection is organized into 5 series; General Information, Programs, Championship Publications, UH Athletic Publications and Miscellaneous Athletic Publications and Clippings. Each series is arranged alphabetically by athletic team or committee, and then chronologically when necessary. Materials range in date from the 1950’s to 2010.
Detailed List of Contents
- General Information
  - Athletics - All Access Pass, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Committee (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Department (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baseball (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Basketball (Men’s) “Cougar Notes” (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Basketball (Men’s), undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Basketball (Men’s), 1950s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Basketball (Men’s), 1960s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Basketball (Men’s), 1970s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Basketball (Men’s), 1980s (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Basketball (Men’s), 2000s (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Basketball (Women’s), undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Basketball (Women’s), 1970s (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Basketball (Women’s), 1980s (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Basketball (Women’s), 2000s (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Boxing, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cheerleading, 2000s (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cougar Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cougar Club, 1950s (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cougar Club, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cougar Club, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cougar Club Membership Handbook (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Basketball (Men’s) “Cougar Notes”, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cougar Club News vol.10 no.2, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cougar Club News vol.11 no.3, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cougar Club News vol.1, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cougar Club News vol.1 no.1, May 14, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cougar Club News vol. 2, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cougar Club News vol.3, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cougar Club News, 1965-1966, Vol. 4 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cougar Club News vol. 5, September 1966-December 1966 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cougar Club News, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Cougar Club News, (National), undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Cougar Club News, (National), 12-11-75, 12-8-76 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cougar Dolls, 2000s (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Cross-Country (Men’s) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cross-Country (Women’s) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Events, 1950s (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Events, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Events, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Events, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Events, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Events, 2000s (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Events - Jog-Walk-Share-athon (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Football, undated (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
  - Football, 1950s (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Football, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Football, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Football, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football, 2000s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football - Andre Ware (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football - Newspaper clippings (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bayou Bucket Coin - Rice vs. Houston, September 4, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5a)
  - Golf (Men’s) - Dave Williams, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Golf (Men’s), undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Golf (Men’s), 1950s (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Golf (Men’s), 1960s (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Golf (Men’s), 1970s (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Golf (Men’s), 1980s (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Golf (Men’s), 1990s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Golf (Men’s), 2000s (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings - Mike Sohaefer (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Golf - Newspaper clippings, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Intramurals (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Soccer (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Softball (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Stationary - Baseball (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Stationary - Basketball (Men’s) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Stationary - Basketball (Women’s) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Stationary - Football (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Stationary - Golf (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Stationary - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Stationary - Soccer (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Stationary - Softball (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Stationary - Sports News (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Stationary - Swimming/Diving (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Stationary - Track (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Stationary - Volleyball (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Student Athletic Handbook, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Student Athletic Handbook, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - SWAIAW Handbook, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - SWAIAW Handbook, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - SWAIAW Handbook, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Swimming (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Swimming (Men’s) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - TAIAW Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - TAIAW Handbook, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Tennis (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ticket Office (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Track, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Track, 1950s (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Track, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Track, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Track, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Track, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Track, 2000s (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Volleyball (Men’s) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Volleyball (Women’s) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Front material, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Schedule of events, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Radio proposals, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Inter-office memos, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Guest lists, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Concessions, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Advertising and signage, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Budget and invoices, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Follow-ups and thank you notes, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - “Basketball Bash” binder - Photos and invitations, 11/5/94 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Programs
  - Baseball
    - (Rosebud Classic), March 15, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Basketball (Men's)
    - Missouri Valley Conference, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Sam Houston St. College, January 18, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Tulsa, January 25, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Loyola University, February 15, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - St. Louis University, March 8, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Oklahoma St., Oklahoma, Texas A&M, December 15-16, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - St. Louis University, January 14,1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Texas A&M, January 19, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Texas Christian University, December 12, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - OLE MISS, December 20, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Lions’ Holiday Classic, December 22-23, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Texas A&M, January 30, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Cincinnati, February 1, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Florida State University, February 5, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - University of Miami, February 8, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Tulsa, February 20, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Baylor, December 8, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Missouri, December 17, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - LSU, (Cougar Holiday Classic), December 21-22, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Texas Christian, January 29, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Minnesota, December 2, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Minnesota, December 18, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bluebonnet Classic, December 13-14, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - UCLA, January 20, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Fairfield University, January 29, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Valparaiso University, February 24, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Tech, March 2, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Southern Mississippi, November 20, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Pepperdine College, December 2, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - University of Arizona, December 5, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Kansas State University, December 16, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - University of Illinois, December 21, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bowling Green University, December 23, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Astro Blue Bonnet Classic, December 27-28, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - West Texas State University, January 4, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Centenary College, January 11,1969 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Texas A&M, January 28, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Notre Dame, February 1, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - University of Nevada (Las Vegas), February 6, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - University of Texas (Arlington), February 8, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - St. Mary’s University, February 13, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Lamar Tech, February 20, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Seattle University, February 22, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Centenary, December 6, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - University of Southern California, December 20, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - California State, December 22, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - West Texas State University, January 10, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Loyola University New Orleans, February 19, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Northwestern State, December 3, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Bluebonnet Classic, December 11-12, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Auburn University, December 21, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - University of Dayton, January 4, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Creighton University, January 6, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - West Texas State, January 9, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Kansas State, December 21, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Louisville, December 2, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - North Carolina, December 7, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - USC, December 16, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Hawaii, January 3-4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - University of Dayton, January 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Rice, January 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Mercer, January 18, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Nevada, January 25, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Stanford, January 27, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - South Carolina, February 1, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Texas Lutheran, February 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Cincinnati, February 8, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Southern Mississippi, February 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - St. Mary’s, February 19, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Lamar, February 22, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Houston Baptist, February 27, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Israel, March 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Cal State Poly, December 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Texas A & I, December 9, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Louisiana Tech, December 20, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Houston Baptist, January 2-3, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Rice, January 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Arkansas, January 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Texas, January 17, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Baylor, January 24, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Texas Tech, January 31, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Houston Baptist, February 3, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Texas Christian, February 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - SMU, February 24, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Texas Lutheran, November 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Trinity, December 11, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Nevada, December 17-18, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Texas Tech, February 1, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Arkansas, February 5, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Texas Lutheran, December 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Xavier (18th Annual Bluebonnet Classic), December 16-17, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - (Postseason Classic III), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Houston Baptist, January 5, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Arkansas, January 6, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Baylor, January 17, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Rice, January 21, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Texas Tech University, January 25, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Texas Christian, February 1, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Texas A&M, February 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Rice, February 11, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Southern Methodist University, February 13, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - University of Arkansas, February 18, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Rice University, February 25, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Windsor, November 18, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Nevada, November 27, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - St. Mary’s, December 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Hardin-Simmons, December 6, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Texas Lutheran, January 3, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Texas A&M, January 10, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Texas Christian, January 13, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Southern Methodist, January 22, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Baylor, February 6, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Rice, February 10, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Texas Tech, February 15, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Arizona, November 30, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Arizona State, December 3, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Texas A&I, December 5, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Texas Lutheran, December 11, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Rice, January 3, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Baylor, January 26, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Texas Tech, January 30, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Arkansas, February 9, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - TCU, February 12, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Texas A&M, February 22, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Pan America, December 13, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - TCU, January 24, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - TCU, February 17, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Rice, February 24, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Biscayne, December 6, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - (2nd Annual Salvation Army Christmas Kettle Classic), December 18-19, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - (PHI SLAMA JAMA), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - SMU, January 8, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Biscayne, December 3, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - St. Mary’s, December 10, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Rice, February 17, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Texas Wesleyan, November 29, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - DePaul, December 12, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - TCU, March 1, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Nevada, December 2, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Texas Tech, January 13, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Baylor, February 17, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Baylor, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Nicholls State; Alcorn State; NW Oklahoma State; Louisiana-Lafayette, November12;14;20;23, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Nevada; UTSA; Sam Houston State; Rogers State, December 6;11;21;30, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - UCF; Tulsa; UTEP, January 8; 19/22, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Marshall; Tulane; SMU, February 1;12;16, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - UAB; Rice, February 26, 2011; March 5, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Football
    - (Annual UH Varsity vs. UH Alumni), Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - (Annual UH Varsity-Exes Spring Game), Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Oregon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - St. Bonaventure, September 23, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4a)
    - Baylor, September 30, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Trinity, October 7, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Louisville, October 15,1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - North Texas, November 11, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - William & Mary, (Homecoming), November 18, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Midwestern, November 24, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Tulsa, December 2, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Baylor, (Homecoming), September 22, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Harding-Simmons, October 20, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Villanova, October 27, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Oklahoma A&M, November 24, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Texas A&M, September 20,1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Tulsa, October 11, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Mississippi, November 8, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Baylor, November 15, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Wyoming, December 6, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Texas A&M, September 26, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - UT Austin, October 3, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Oklahoma A&M, October 17, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Arizona State, October 24, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Texas Tech, November 21, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Tennessee, December 15, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Baylor, September 18, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Texas A&M, October 9, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Tulsa, November 6, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Mississippi University, November 13, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Arkansas, November 27, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Detroit, December 4, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Texas A&M, October 1, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Wichita University, October 29, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Villanova University, November 19, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Mississippi, Sept 19, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Mississippi State, September 29, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Alabama, September 26, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Cincinnati, October 3, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - North Texas State, October 24, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Mississippi, September 17, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Texas A&M, October 8, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Oklahoma State, October 15, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Cincinnati, November 5, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Tulsa, November 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Baylor, September 22, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Boston, October 7, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Alabama, (Homecoming), October 28, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Florida State, November 25, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Oregon State, December 2, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Texas A&M, September 29, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mississippi State, October 20, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Tulsa, (Homecoming), November 10, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Cincinnati, December 1, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Auburn, September 21, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Mississippi, October 5, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Detroit, November 2, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Trinity, September 12, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Texas A&M, September 25, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Tulsa, October 10, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Florida State, November 7, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Penn State, November 14, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Cincinnati University, November 28, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Tulsa, September 11, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Mississippi State, September 18, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Cincinnati, September 24, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Chattanooga, October 30, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Washington State, September 23, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Mississippi State, September 30, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Oklahoma State, October 1, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Mississippi State, October 15, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Tampa, October 29, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Tulsa, November 5, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Memphis, November 26, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Utah, December 3, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Florida State, September 15, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Wake Forest, September 29, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Florida State, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Tulsa, November 23, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Mississippi State, October 4, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Auburn (Astro Bluebonnet Bowl), December 31, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Ole Miss., October 25, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Tulsa, October 31, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Wake Forest, November 21, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Cincinnati, November 25,1972 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Rice, September 15, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - (Red & White Spring Game), April 20, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Miami, September 21, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Villanova, October 19, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Cincinnati, October 25, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Memphis State, November 16, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - North Carolina (Astro-Blubonnet Bowl), December 23, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Virginia Tech, November 8, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Arkansas, October 23, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Rice, November 27, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Miami, December 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Maryland (Cotton Bowl Classic), January 1, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - UCLA, September 12, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Utah, September 23, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Baylor, October 1, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Baylor, October 7, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - SMU, October 15, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Texas, November 5, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Texas Tech, November 19, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Utah, September 23, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Texas A&M, October 14, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Arkansas, (Homecoming), October 28, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - TCU, November 4, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Florida, September 15, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - West Texas State, September 29, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Baylor, October 6, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Texas A&M, October 13, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - SMU, October 20, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - TCU, November 3, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Texas Tech, November 24, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Nebraska (Cotton Bowl Classic), January 1, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Miami-Florida, September 20, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - North Texas State, September 27, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Arkansas, October 25, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - TCU, November 1, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Navy (Garden State Bowl), December 14, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - (24th Annual Red & White Spring Game), April 24, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - New Mexico, September 5, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Utah State, September 26, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)